citiclassifieds.com 2009-04-24

# CitiClassifieds.com - Privacy Policy

  |   
---|---  
  
###  Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting CitiClassifieds.com website. CitiClassifieds.com know that you care about how the information about you is used and shared. This policy explains our practices regarding the privacy of those who visit our Website.   
  
---  
  
**The Information We Collect**

* * *

Generally, the only information that CitiClassifieds.com collects about you is that which you provide us voluntarily. We record the e-mail address of those who communicate with us through e-mail. If you supply us with your e-mail address via on-line registration, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. Any personally identifiable information that you provide to us will not be sold or shared to third parties unless such sharing is expressly authorized by you, required by law or as covered by this policy. If you are simply visiting or navigating our Website, CitiClassifieds.com will not collect, sell or share any of your personally identifiable information. Our web server may collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information from you, such as your domain name, IP address and the type of browser you are using. Such information is gathered for statistical purposes only so that we may better understand our visitors' interests and preferences as well as for computer maintenance and security purposes.

We may, in the future, use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. For more on changes in our information practices, please see the paragraph below titled "Changes to this Policy".   
  
**Information Sharing**

* * *

Unless your prior consent has been obtained, CitiClassifieds.com will not provide your personal information to third parties. However, in any of the following cases CitiClassifieds.com may provide personal information to third parties without your prior consent. 

  * If CitiClassifieds.com is required to do so by law. 
  * If it is necessary to do so in order to protect the lives of persons or properties. 
  * If it is necessary to cooperate with central government institutions, local governments, or any entities acting on their behalf for the execution of any legally prescribed business, and there is concern that obtaining your consent may impede the execution of the said business.

**Data Security**

* * *

We take precautions to insure that the information you submit to us via the web is as secure as reasonably possible from unauthorized use or access. CitiClassifieds.com has implemented physical, electronic and managerial procedures to keep any personal information disclosed to us by our users secure and to disclose such information only after obtaining permission from the user (except under the circumstances discussed above).

Please note that the web is an open system, therefore, while we take measures to protect your information once it has been submitted to us, we cannot guarantee the security of e-mails sent to us while they are in transit. Therefore, if you wish to communicate sensitive information to us, we recommend calling us instead of using e-mail.   
  
**Other Websites**

* * *

This Website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or maintained by CitiClassifieds.com. These links are included for your convenience and if you choose to link to one of these websites, your privacy with respect to such sites will be governed by their respective privacy polices and practices and not by CitiClassifieds.com's privacy policy.   
  
**Changes To This Policy**

* * *

As our Privacy Policy may change from time to time, be sure to check this Website frequently to view changes to this page.
